I
Hey, Clark.
Whatcha doing?
Hey, um, I'm just trying to figure out some of this trade homework.
What for? Don't you already have a scholarship to Met U?
Yes, for football. But they're still gonna be looking at my final GPA.
Oh, when you're done playing with your protractor, there's a party over at Katie's house.
Her parents have a hot tub.
Really?
Yeah.
Um, thanks, but I still got a lot of work to do here.
Okay.
Well, why don't you drop by later if you feel like it?
You finished?
See ya.
Bye, Clark.
Hey.
There's a party over at Katie's house.
Yeah, she was cute.
Which one?
Both.
Thinking of asking one of them out?
Yeah, so then I can ruin it just when we're getting close by having to lie about who I really am.
Just like I did with Lana?
Clark, there is someone out there for you.
Who?
Mom and girl would have to be crazy to get in a relationship with me.
I can't believe they're thinking about letting that psycho go.
That is what generally happens when a patient is cured.
A patient?
Iust to ourっ
Don't care how you do it, just stay, stay.
Come on, I've been waiting for you.
I've made this whole world shine for you.
Just stay, stay.
Come on.
So what's Smallville's star quarterback doing up here alone on a Saturday night?
Alicia.
I'm surprised you remember my name.
How could I forget?
You tried to kill me and Lana.
I'd asked how you escaped, but I guess I'd have to say you're not.
I'm sorry.
I thought you were a cop.
I thought I was a cop.
But you never told me that.
No, that's pretty obvious.
I didn't escape.
They let me out.
The doctors say I'm cured.
You could've called instead of teleporting into my loft.
Actually, I borrowed my mom's car and I drove.
It's a little something my doctor came up with.
Trace amounts of lead are released into my blood stream and it keeps me from using my
powers.
I'm glad you're okay.
I'm glad they think you're better.
That doesn't change what happened between us.
I know that, Clark.
I just wanted to tell you how sorry I am for everything I put you through.
You're the last person on Earth that I ever wanted to hurt.
But you didn't answer my question.
Why are you up here alone on a Saturday night?
I don't know.
Maybe I prefer to be alone.
Because of your secret?
Don't worry, I didn't tell anyone.
I had promised you that I wouldn't.
Alicia.
The whole time I was in Belle Reve,
just the thought that there was someone out there like me
who knew what it was like to be different.
It gave me hope.
In my darkest moment, you gave me hope, Clark.
Bye.
So they just let Alicia teleport out of Belle Reve?
No, they gave her some sort of lead bracelet
that stops her from using her powers,
and she doesn't seem as dangerous anymore.
Her powers weren't the only thing that made her dangerous, Clark.
She's obsessed with you.
And she knows your secret, which she kept for over a year.
Whatever they did to her in Belle Reve, maybe it worked.
We know how much you want to be with someone
you don't have to lie to, sweetheart,
but Alicia isn't the one.
So what should I do, just wait for the next cute girl with special abilities to knock on my door?
Clark, you know what she did.
Alicia needs to be in an institution.
Then why'd they let her out of Belle Reve?
What if she really is better?
What if she isn't?
Damn, I'm good.
All right, Alicia Baker.
Suffering from a histrionic personality disorder causing emotional instability resulting in psychotic episodes.
Yeah, that's our girl.
Who's that guy?
It's Alicia's psychiatrist, Dr. William McBride.
Yeah, I've heard of him.
He graduated from Harvard in two years with more degrees than a thermometer.
What's he say about Alicia?
Well, according to Dr. McBride, Alicia really is cured.
She was telling the truth.
And that, I take it, is exactly what our young Mr. Kent wanted to hear.
Yeah.
What are you doing here?
It's nice to see you, too.
Sorry, I just didn't expect you to show up on campus.
Like I didn't expect you to say that you needed space right before you walked out on me?
Jason, what's really going on here?
Where this is heading with us?
I just don't think...
I don't think you're ready.
I don't think you're ready for a relationship like that.
Relationship like what?
Can we not talk about this right now?
I don't want...
Look, Lana, I have to go.
Okay.
The thing is, like I'm the kind of guy who is free to change my mind, HealthyWay,
and she wasn't with me at the time when I think Estado was
the I was walking back and forth.
Cool?
Well, you were sick then, and I understand now.
I don't.
I mean, I remember feeling angry and alone
and doing all those things, but...
I don't know, when I think about it now, it's like...
It's like watching a movie like it wasn't even really me.
Maybe it wasn't.
Maybe this is the real you.
Oh, God!
Good thing you've got buns of steel.
Oh, you might be impervious to the cold,
but I'm turning into a popsicle.
Well, I do have heat vision.
I think I'd settle for some hot chocolate.
Okay.
I'm just gonna go freshen up first.
I'll meet you over there.
Okay.
Enjoying your freedom?
Oh, Dr. McBride.
What are you doing here?
Checking up on my favorite patient.
This does more than just keep you in place, Alicia.
You lowjacked me?
I have to know where you are
so that you don't do anything to jeopardize your release.
Like associating with Clark Kent.
What I do with Clark is my own business.
Clark was the object of your obsession, Alicia.
Your feelings for him are what precipitated your psychotic break.
I'm sorry.
You really want to risk an incident like that again?
You said that I was better.
And I want you to stay that way.
Perhaps more sessions together outside of the office would be beneficial.
You are such a bright and beautiful young girl.
Be ashamed to see me like this.
Be ashamed to see you end up back in Bellevue.
Stop seeing Clark Kent before someone gets hurt.
There you are.
I thought I'd lost you.
You're not getting rid of me that easily.
Oh, I'm gonna get cold.
Do you mind?
Me?
I don't know if you can get out of this cold.
It's just a thought.
Only a thought.
But if my life is for rent
And I don't want to try
So what do you want to do next?
Um, you want to go for a drive?
Sure.
Where do you want to go?
Have you ever been to California?
California?
Sure, let's jump in the truck and we'll go to California right now.
Are you serious?
At least you going to California would be...
Crazy?
I wasn't gonna say that.
No, I know that it sounds crazy, I just...
I just wanna go somewhere where nobody knows me.
What I did...
I want you to come with me.
I can.
I mean, as much as I'd wanna be with you.
Is everything okay?
I actually have to go.
Sorry. I'll call you later.
Okay.
Such a big tämä
habit thankful to everyone's support
while you are signала
Oh, the prodigal father returns.
I've been trying to reach you, but you're always somehow unavailable.
Too busy playing with your sword to speak to your father?
Actually, I've been preoccupied by your court papers.
I'm trying to unravel how you managed to get your conviction overturned.
I don't think you'll find the answers in a stack of legal documents.
It was a miracle. There's no other way to explain it.
And I must use that freedom I was given towards a greater purpose.
Well, I hope that purpose doesn't include returning to Luthor Corps,
because you won't be walking through the door
to the executive office.
I don't want to be in the executive suite
or reading the coffers to line your pockets anytime soon.
I'm not here for money, Lex.
I don't want to take Luthor Corp away from you.
Corporate maneuvering doesn't interest me anymore.
So what, now trying to kill me is going to be a full-time job?
I know where you're coming from, Lex.
It's a place of anger and mistrust.
But it's not too late. It's not.
There's still time to get off the path that can only lead to darkness.
Come on, Dad.
What are you really up to?
I am trying to make the world a better place.
I'm going to create a charitable foundation.
Not just to feed the hungry and clothe the poor.
I want to really help people, to inspire the human spirit.
I wish everyone on the face of the Earth could be as blessed as I am.
So now you're the Messiah?
No.
Lex, no, I'm just...
I'm a man who has a dream.
Oh, guess who?
I was starting to think you were on your way to California already.
My bags are in the car.
What's going on?
Uh...
Dr. McBride, my psychiatrist, he was at the ice rink.
He said that if I keep seeing you, he's going to send me back to Belle Reve.
Why would he do that?
Maybe because he's jealous.
I think in his mind, he thought that if I was out, he could be with me.
Well, go to the review board at Belle Reve and tell them about McBride.
I can't risk them revoking your offer.
I can't risk them revoking my probation.
What do you think they're going to do if you run?
As long as I'm free, I don't care.
Come with me, Clark.
I want to.
But running's not the answer.
Trust me, I know.
I wish I was as strong as you are.
But I'm not.
Um...
I made something for you in Belle Reve for when I got out.
Alicia.
I guess now it's a... it's a goodbye present.
Would you mind wearing it so I can see it on you just once?
Hey.
I missed you in A.P. Lit today. What happened?
Did you decide you just couldn't face the love songs of J. Alfred Prufrock?
No. Um...
I went to go see Jason.
I'm sensing it didn't go so well.
Sorry.
But, uh, Poker Face isn't exactly your story.
Strong suit.
What's up?
I think I finally figured out why he's been so cryptic.
He doesn't think that I'm ready for that kind of a relationship.
What? What kind?
Oh, that kind.
Oh, okay.
Okay.
Wow.
That answers a question I've been dying to ask you all semester.
Does everybody think that we've...
Lana.
You were alone with him for three months in Paris.
Yeah.
Right.
Um...
Well, we haven't.
But I'm starting to think that I'm ready.
I'm sorry.
If you can't go with her, you both are already together now.
Well...
And looking into who I am makes it impossible.
만들 it?
Sorry, but I got an idea that probably got me worried outside of work.
Why won't I leave?
No, I have to make her understand.
I think I'm friends with Daphan.
I can interpret it better than make her feel that I still don't understand.
I don't really support her speaking my mind.
Well, sorry, I've been very busy as a nurse,
It's okay.
Sometimes this...
No, don't.
regret doing it too soon.
And on behalf of that two-thirds,
just be sure that you're really ready.
Wait a minute.
Are you saying that you've...
Yeah.
During my internship at the Daily Planet,
his name was Jimmy.
He was very cute in a bow-tie kind of way.
You know, I mean, it was a summer infatuation
that I thought was the real thing.
Do you wish you hadn't done it?
Sometimes.
I mean, it wasn't awful by any means,
but it just wasn't special.
And as cliche as it sounds, it only happens once.
So just make sure Jason's the guy
that you want to remember forever.
Do you ever feel like breaking down?
Do you ever feel out of place?
Like somehow you just don't belong
And no one understands you
Do you ever want to run away?
Do you lock yourself in your room?
With the radio on, turn it up so loud
That no one hears you screaming
Can we just slow down a little bit?
I want this to last forever.
I'm not sure that's one of my abilities,
but I'll do my best.
I'm sorry.
What?
Uh...
What is it?
I'm a virgin.
That's great.
So am I.
I love you.
Really?
Mm-hmm.
What?
It's just, we don't have any kind of commitment or anything.
Oh.
Maybe no one is more committed to making this happen than me.
You are the most beautiful, amazing, sexiest girl I've ever met.
And there's no way I'm letting you get away.
You just don't mean that you want me to be your girlfriend.
No.
I want you to be my wife.
You're done.
Make your suburban alrededor melt and colour what it's like.
Are you serious?
Yeah.
We were mean to be together.
We could be in Vegas tonight and wake up Mr.. Mrs and the ST.
And you could't be in Vegas tonight and be in Las Vegas.
Oh my God.
There we are.
We're gonna kiss too.
There are days, weeks and years
however to hold to these memories.
Then we're gonna live.
And I wasn't this young if I lived.
Then I have it, Heidi.
You know me.
When I was...
Welcome to my life
We are gathered here to join this sappy couple in holy matrimony.
Marriage, as you know, is a union that should not be entered in too lightly.
Yeah, yeah, skip to the good stuff, Pops.
Oh, all right.
Do you, Clark Kent, take this woman to be your lawfully wedded wife?
Hell yes.
And do you, Alicia Baker, take this man to be your lawfully wedded husband?
I do.
Well, you may kiss the...
Oh, I see you're already doing that.
Well, by the power invested in me by the state of Nevada,
I now pronounce you man and wife.
Oh, my God.
My head is swimming.
Don't drown just yet.
Oh, my God, I can't believe this.
I'm Mrs. Clark Kent.
Let's make it official.
Ah!
Jason, you're early.
Well, I got your message.
It sounded like an emergency,
so I came as soon as I could.
This isn't exactly how I planned it.
Sigh.
I need you to look me in the eye and tell me that you don't love me.
Then there's no good reason why we shouldn't be together.
Okay, I'm gonna stop you.
Um...
Not that I wouldn't love for this to happen...
but it can't.
I mean, not like this.
Uh... okay, I don't understand.
Um, I thought that you broke up with me be-
because...
Okay, all right, um...
I haven't been completely honest with you.
There's someone else.
No.
Um, no.
Then what is it, Jason?
Why did you just walk out on this relationship?
Because I don't think we met by accident.
I think that my mother arranged it.
How's that even possible?
My mother was-
the one who convinced me to go to Paris in the first place.
She said that I would meet someone special, and I did.
And then everything started happening,
the tattoo and Isabelle's tomb and the spellbook.
None of it made any sense
until you saw my mother in your nightmare
about Isabelle being burned at the stake.
No, that was just a bad dream, that's all.
Or maybe it was your subconscious connecting the dots.
Either way, I didn't want my mother to use me to get close to you,
so, uh...
Jason, whatever's going on,
it doesn't change the way that I feel about you.
Yeah.
I'm not doing fine
I'm disintegrating lies
I've blown the phone booth of a lady
Shaky heinous crime
They left hands on two floorboards
Saying he's psyched, I know they're bored
And I'm bored, still bored
I'm so bored
I got a funny little feeling
My arms are shaking like a lightning rod, yeah
I'm getting bored in this feeling
Let's see my teeth until the feeling's gone, yeah
Oh, I'm a slow-mo guy
No time for swallowing flies
I'm freezing bees, knees, E's and G's
String C's and E's and funny little feeling
Lick it dry, wonder just who am I?
Prison-molding teenage boy
Transvestite with high heels on
Hey, where is my lock on?
Ain't done anything I want
According to my list
I've still got so many musicians to kill
Will kill until I feel my way
Feel for the body standing still
Got a funny little feeling
Yeah, yeah
I'm shaking like a lightning rod, yeah
I'm getting bored in this feeling
Let's see my teeth until the feeling's gone
I love you so much
I know how you feel
Wait
Wait, we're half the way, we're married
No
I just want this to be right
I want all of you
No I really need somebody else
I really need some money
I need don't pick up
You could do everything
You could do
Right here
You could do everything
It's over
Clark didn't do anything.
What are you doing here?
Alicia, get out of here.
Don't tell her what to do.
Clark, I know I made a huge mistake.
You're the only person who's ever really known me.
Alicia.
And when I'm with you, I feel normal.
I'll always love you for that.
No, I'm not gonna let him keep hurting you.
You don't know what you're talking about.
This stops now.
Alicia.
We should probably get to a hospital, don't you think?
Alicia, why'd you do that?
You know I could've caught that bullet.
Because I promised you that I'd always protect your secret.
I'm sorry.
Hey.
How are you feeling?
Like I just teleported in front of a bullet.
Yeah.
The doctor said you could be released today.
You might want to hold the jokes until then.
What happened to Dr. McBride?
They're holding him for observation at Belle Reve
or trying to kill one of his patients.
I'm so sorry about what I did to you, Clark.
I guess I just didn't want to lose the one good thing in my life.
I'm not so sure that drugging me was the best way to preserve the relationship.
I wanted you with or without that rock.
I'll talk to him tomorrow.
I'll walk you home.
I'll wait for you again.
Say goodbye.
planets don't go that far.
Yeah.
Yes.
I really am sorry.
You know that, right?
Yeah, I know.
Oh, warm fire on a cold night.
There's nothing like it, is there?
Thanks for coming by, Dad.
I know how busy you are with saving the world.
I was hoping that your call was an olive branch
that we could reconcile,
but obviously...
Obviously, I was wrong.
Where are you going, Dad?
Back to the motel out by the interstate?
Or, hey, it's almost dinner time.
You might still be able to make it to the mission
for your evening bowl of soup.
They also serve a surprisingly tasty Salisbury steak.
You know, I gotta hand it to you, Dad.
When you throw yourself into a role,
you really commit.
This is not an act, Lex.
You should know that by now.
You've been having me followed since I was released.
Which you knew I would.
I'm not playing at some elaborate game, Lex.
This is my life now.
You've stripped me of every penny I once had,
and I'm making the best of it.
And you're right.
It's, uh...
It's about time for my evening bowl of soup.
Dad...
You can stay in the guest house.
Thanks.
It'll be much easier keeping an eye on me.
Good night, Dad.
Good night.
Is Dad still upset?
What do you think?
How about you?
I'm upset.
But more than that, I'm disappointed.
I was on red kryptonite, Mom.
My God, you ran off with a girl you barely know and got married.
It wasn't legal.
That's not even the point.
Marriage is sacred, Clark.
It's about two people who trust each other
and are willing to go through life together no matter how difficult it gets.
I thought we had taught you that.
You're an amazing young man, Clark.
You make life and death decisions every day.
But then you turn around and you do this.
Why did you do it?
Mom, there's a part of me that never feels freer than when I'm with Alicia.
She makes me feel normal and special at the same time.
I know how badly you want to be with somebody.
I want that for you, too.
I guess...
I just expected you to use better judgment.
Guess I know why you're alone.
Hey, Alicia.
What's going on?
What did you say?
Do you notice me so released?
Anyways, you'll be home by me cool as new.
It's you, Jack?
scarcity.
I'm the one who shops?
Yeah.
I have faith in you.
Look, I know that we can never be together after what I did.
But it doesn't change how I feel.
And I just wanted you to know that
for as long as I live, I'm never going to reveal your secret.
I love you.
That's all.
Alicia, wait.
Wait.
I love you.